One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Beyond the heavy rain is a rainbow
hageshii ame no mukou kakaru niji wo mita
I'll know the easy answer's a lie
tayasui kotae wa uso dato shiru darou
Vow not to back down to the shouting
dekai koe nanka ni makenai to chikatte
I need you alone to understand tomorrow
anata hitori ni wakatte hoshii ashita
You gave me the time of my life
yume no youna jikan kureta anata
What do I look like? An ANGEL or a DEVIL...
watashi wa dou mieteruno? sorega tenshi ka akuma ka
Beyond the dawn, beyond the dawn
yoake no mukou yoake no mukou
There's so much I want to tell you
hanashitai koto takusan arun da
Filled with love, with love
ai kometa ai kometa
That can't be written down in a letter
tegami ni kakikirenai omoi da
A small hand in search of eternity
eien wo sagashita chiisana tenohira
Baltigo, Revolutionary
Army Headquarters
Requesting aid!
The rebels in Tumi in the South Blue
are becoming outnumbered!
Please come to our aid immediately!
I repeat!
The rebels in Tumi in the South Blue
are becoming outnumbered!
Please come to our aid immediately!
We can't go!
We're carrying a lot of injured people
from the Goa Kingdom!
Iva-chan, I'll go.
No, Kuma! You've been too reckless...
...since then!
Kuma!
Wait!
Tumi, South Blue
Damn!
This is it, rebels!
Is he our ally?
Ginny got abducted?!
Yes... Seems like a Celestial Dragon
had his eye on her...
She was taken away by a Government ship
to be that Celestial Dragon's wife.
Ursa Shock.
The Revolutionary Army?
A-Amazing!
Three years of fighting
has finally paid off!
All thanks to the Revolutionary Army!
They're the common people's heroes!
Our unit was wiped out
by an unexpected raid.
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Dragon, it's me.
I'm tired...
I'll take a ship home.
"A Pledge to Ginny -
Kuma Becomes a Father"
About two years had passed...
...since Ginny, the
Revolutionary Army captain,
was kidnapped to be a Celestial
Dragon's wife...
I'm sorry.
We're here, Bonney.
Kuma! We've got a call from Ginny!
Move it, babes!
Ginny!
Big Bro?
Hey, Kumachi!
I'm back in the lower world!
Oh! You had us worried!
Ginny... I'm glad that you're alive!
Yeah...
I got sick...
I became unwanted, so I was discarded.
Lucky me!
Sick?
What do you mean by that, Ginny?
I wanted to see you all again,
but this is me saying goodbye.
Huh?!
W-What are you talking about, Ginny?!
I thought I'd never see you again!
Where are you?! I'll be there right away!
I'm sorry, Kumachi.
I'm dying. It won't be long.
What?
You're dying?
Why?
Why?!
I'll save you!
I'll leave now!
Kumachi.
I appreciate your kindness,
but don't ever come to see me.
Ginny! We'll be right there to help you!
Where are you?!
Move it!
Kuma!
Where are you going?!
There's only one place she'd come back to!
Dragon, Big Bro...
Kumachi is too kind.
Please watch over him.
And Kumachi...
I'll always...
...always...
...love you.
Kuma? You're back?!
Where's Ginny?! I know she's here!
She is, but...
Ginny!
Why... What happened to you?!
Her face and entire body...
She said when exposed to natural light,
her skin would turn blue and hard like stone.
Poor child...
I wonder what happened to her.
Kumachi!
Yummy!
Let's get married, Kumachi!
I promise I'll make you happy!
Kumachi!
To make sure her baby could live
even if something happened to her...
...she crossed the sunny seas to get here
while she was still alive.
Don't worry, Ginny.
I'll raise your daughter.
No!
The bottle is at the wrong angle!
H-H-How's this?
Oh, sorry!
Are you trying to drown her?!
Let me do it!
Put her in an iron cage when you sleep.
You might crush her with your massive body.
She's really cute.
You drink a lot, Bonney-chan.
She'll grow up to be a glutton
just like Ginny.
I want more.
Yeah, she will...
Before I knew it, she made it that far away.
I have to keep my eyes on her!
Yes! That's it, Bonney!
D...
Daddy!
Yes, I'm your daddy!
Hey! Bonney!
Oh, you're home!
Welcome home!
Kuma?!
Why are you boarding up
all the windows in the church?!
Close the door!
Look at this.
Blue stones?!
This is...
Just like when Ginny died--
Don't say it!
I'll go get the doctor!
Please do...
Well...
When exposed to the sun?
Really?
Yes.
Let's take her out and see--
Don't be ridiculous!
It's not White Lead Disease...
I'm sorry. I've never seen this symptom.
I see...
Dad?
Don't worry, Bonney.
You're quitting the Revolutionary Army?!
Does Bonney really have
the same disease as her mother?!
Yeah...
I don't know what to do...
...but I want to be with her.
I understand.
Live your life without regrets.
We'll ask every doctor
in the world that we can.
Thank you, Dragon!
Seven
Seven Years Ago
Time passed, and when Bonney was five...
Run!
The vampire will eat us alive!
Bonney (Age 5)
Get lost, you little punks!
Nyaaa!
Ha! You can't go farther than this point!
You're a vampire who can't go outside!
Take this cross! Sheeen!
Ouch!
You're in a church!
You want me to chase you out there?!
Wait, Bonney!
Dad.
Please don't go outside. Even just
seeing you at the door makes me nervous.
You're such a chicken.
I was just joking.
Well, don't do it, even as a joke.
All right.
I don't wanna make you sad.
Bonney!
You've grown up to be a good girl!
Stop it, you crybaby!
Those punks...
...made fun of the stones on my face!
Is it that weird?
But it's a disease. I can't help it.
Those jewels?!
You scared me!
They're just jealous,
because they're so beautiful.
What?
You think so?!
Yes! I love them!
Bonney, if you were to travel after you
got well, where would you want to go?
Oh! Do you know about Sky Islands?
There are islands in the sky?
That's right! I saw it in a book!
See?!
Sky Islands are closer to the sun,
so maybe Nika will be there!
I bet you'd be excited about that, Daddy!
Nika, huh?!
Here we go! Nika's dance!
It's going to be a big adventure
to go up in the sky!
Should we do it when you turn 20?
Okay!
Where are we going when you turn 19?
Fish-Man Island!
Your daughter's symptom... It's an
incurable disease called Sapphire Scales.
You know what it is?
Yes.
I'm sorry, but keep your voice down.
I've heard of very few cases recently.
Sunlight and moonlight, all kinds of
natural light will cause the stones to spread.
But even if you avoid the light completely,
it'll still progress.
What?
Is it really incurable?!
Bonney...
My daughter has a way to survive, right?!
I'm going to be honest with you.
Your daughter...
...has five years at most to live.
She won't live to see her tenth birthday.
Can't you do something about it?
There is no known cure at this time.
Ten years old?!
No way...
But she is growing up to be so healthy!
Isn't there a cure?
Are they sure there isn't?!
What?! Bonney!
I thought you were sleeping!
I heard that!
What?
Ten years old?
Ten years old? What about it?
I heard someone say ten years old!
Oh? Are you crying a little bit?
It was about me, wasn't it?!
Y-Yeah...
Ten years... Ten years old...
About your disease, Bonney...
That doctor said you wouldn't get well
until you turn ten years old.
What?
I was just disappointed
that it would take that long.
Yay!
I'll get well when I turn ten years old?!
Can I go on a trip with you?!
O-Of course you can!
You'll get better when you turn ten.
Ya-hoo!
Oh, no... What have I done?
Then another year passed,
and the nightmare returned to
the Sorbet Kingdom.
Kuma!
Kumachi, help!
King Bekori did it again!
It's 16 years ago all over again!
He's gonna burn alive everyone he thinks
is weighing the country down!
He's inhuman!
He's started slaughtering people!
I can't protect anyone again
mata daremo mamorenai no
It's my fault that the voice is fading away
kiekakaru koe wa boku no sei
I don't even have time to look down
utsumuku hima mo nai no
Gravel marks on my palms
tenohira ni tsuku jari no ato
Start moving again, my ship
mata ugokidase boku no fune yo
Though I can't fly in the broad sky
hiroi sora wa tobenai kedo
I can light up the deep sea
fukai umi wa teraseru kara
We
bokura wa
EVERYDAY owarenai
EVERYDAY, can't let this be the end
EVERYDAY makerenai
EVERYDAY, can't be defeated
We have something here to protect
mamoru mono ga koko niwa aru
This may not be what I expected
yosou chigai kamo?
But we can't stop now
tomarenai yo mou
We go on, sharing loneliness
kodoku wo ima wakeai susumu
Don't be afraid
ojikedukuna yo
I'm not the same person I was that day
ano hi no boku to chigau kara
No one can stand in my way
dare nimo jama dekinai yo
Now, move aside
saa doite
Conquer the world, believe in the future
sekai wo seishite mirai wo shinjite
Count up the nights
ikutsu mono yoru kazoete
What did you see? What did you learn?
nani wo mite nani wo shitte
To realize what was important
taisetsu na koto ni kiduita no